♪ ♪
♪ Mairzy doats and dozy
doats and liddle lamzy divey ♪
♪ A kiddley divey
too, wouldn't you? ♪
Hi!
Hi. ♪ Mairzy doats and dozy
doats and liddle lamzy divey... ♪
Seen today's "Peach Pit"?
What's that?
The comic strip.
I don't read the funnies.
Who'd you vote for in
the state senate election?
♪ Do do do do do. ♪
Peter Dolan.
Then you should start
reading the funnies.
Huh.
That looks just like him.
That's the whole idea.
Who's he talking to?
Some married woman.
Up till now, she's just
been a voice on the phone,
but it looks like we're
finally going to see her.
Huh.
It says the artist is going
to take a couple days off.
Milking the suspense.
Everybody in Georgia's
dying to know who she is.
Oh, he wouldn't draw a person
that people would recognize.
Sure, he would.
Well, that would be libel.
Defamation of character.
Not if it's true.
Ron Winfield's been doing
this strip for seven years.
He's never, ever lost a suit.
Huh.
It's a lie.
So, we sue him.
No. No, I don't want to sue him.
I want to stop him.
You know, if and
when he puts a face
on this mystery
woman he's invented,
it's going to be too late.
The damage will have
already been done.
Well, until he
crosses that line,
I'm afraid we have
no legal recourse.
I can't believe the creep
has a right to do this.
Now, you're my lawyer,
Sam. Do something.
Now, Pete, look, I guarantee it.
The minute he makes
a claim in his strip
which he cannot prove,
we'll hit him with a lawsuit
that'll make him sorry
he ever learned to draw.
You better get going, dear.
I thought you had a meeting.
Yes. Yes, I do.
We have that fundraiser tonight.
I'll try to get home early.
I'll keep trying.
Let me know as soon as
you get a hold of his lawyer.
Yeah.
Did you see it?
Yes, I did.
What are we going to do?
Well, the thing we absolutely
cannot afford to do is panic.
My whole career
is about to go up in flames.
Peter, he not only knew
the name of the hotel,
he knew the room number.
Well, maybe he's, uh...
Maybe he's not
going to expose you.
Maybe he's going
to keep you offstage
the whole time, huh?
Ron Winfield never
pulled a punch in his life,
and you know it.
Look, we-we don't have
all the facts yet.
We've got to stay calm.
How can I?
I'm the one who's
cheating. I'm the one
who's going to look like a
tramp in this thing, not you.
Sandra, I love you,
and no matter what happens,
I'm not going to
abandon you. I promise.
I'm sorry.
I-I'm just so angry
and I'm scared.
Well, you let me handle
things, and try... try not to worry.
Peter?
Yeah.
I love you.
Ron Winfield's office.
Why, I don't know,
Senator Dolan.
I just got in myself. I'll
check to see if he's here.
No, sir, he's not.
May I take a message?
I'm not quite familiar
with that word, Senator.
Would you mind spelling it?
Yes, sir. I'll be
sure and tell him.
He said that if you don't get
back to him within the hour,
you'll be...
roughly paraphrased,
in deep trouble.
Okay.
Ron Winfield's office.
Uh, I don't know,
Senator Hopkins.
I just got in myself. I'll
check to see if he's in.
Do you have anything to say
to the husband of
Senator Dolan's lover?
I'm sorry, sir.
He's not in. May I
take a messa... ge?
God, I'm good.
Actually, I'd make
the lines a little bolder.
You know, there's a moment
when all my assistants decide
they're just as
talented as I am.
Is that what we're
talking about here?
I think I'm a better draftsman.
You are, but don't
let it go to your head.
It's not enough. What you
need is an instinct for the jugular,
dedication to
concept, the message.
I'm gonna miss my plane.
So, who you going after now?
You'll see.
Ink the prints. That's
all you want me to do?
Yeah, right. And, uh, uh...
Feed Otis. Feed Otis.
I'll call you when I get back.
Bye.
What time did he call?
Oh.
All right, all right. What else?
I don't need that.
All right. That's it?
Okay. All right. Thanks!
Are you Ron Winfield?
Well, hello, Senator.
All by yourself tonight?
Come on in.
A little early to be canvassing
the neighborhood for votes,
isn't it, Senator?
You know why I'm here.
No.
It's too heavy.
I don't like this. Get him down.
Get him off me.
Otis, over there and lie down.
Does that to everyone.
Don't feel flattered.
I don't.
Let's talk about your next
comic strip, Mr. Winfield.
Okay. Let's.
When you two are alone,
do you call Miss Hopkins
Sandra or Sandy?
I'm a stickler for details.
You can't do this.
Already have.
I think I got the hairdo
down pretty good,
don't you think?
You're going to ruin both
of us if you publish that.
You are an elected
official and so is she.
The public has a right
to know these things.
Why? We're not criminals.
Why?
She's a married woman.
It's people like you who are
destroying the moral fabric
of this great nation.
Driving that most precious
of American institutions...
The family... to the
brink of extinction.
Oh, please spare me.
However, the fact
of the matter is,
no one outside myself and
my assistant has seen this,
so maybe we can make a deal.
You want to make a deal?
Blackmail?
You piece of trash. Hey,
Senator, let's not
start throwing stones.
You're the one who's got
this thing about sleeping
with his colleague's wife.
How much do you want?
Ooh.
Money's not everything.
You don't want
me to publish this...
give me something bigger
and better to replace it.
I see.
Trade my dirt for somebody
else's dirt, is that it?
Yeah.
Forget it.
Well, then, Senator,
I guess I'll see you...
in the funny papers.
Hey!
Ow!
Yeah, sure, go ahead, take it!
I'll just draw another one,
Einstein!
Oh, yeah, uh...
yeah, okay, thanks, Otis.
Come on, Otis.
What do you mean,
you think you killed him?
All I know is that...
he hit me, I hit him,
and he fell back
and hit his head,
hard, on the fireplace.
Did you knock him
out? No. He, uh,
he was dazed, but he
was never unconscious.
At least... not before I left.
Well, what were you doing there?
I came to beg him not to run
the next installment
of his comic strip.
Oh, yeah, the one
where he was gonna say
who the woman is
that you're seeing.
He even tried to
blackmail me, but then...
that's when I got
mad, grabbed the strip
and took off.
After you punched him out.
Mm-hmm.
Looks like Sandra Hopkins.
That's who it is.
The State Superintendent
of Schools?
Yes.
Senator David Hopkins' wife?
That's who you've been
having an affair with?
Yes.
It wasn't something I set
out to do; it just happened.
How did this Winfield
fellow find out?
I have no idea.
Huh. But he was
alive when you left?
Mm-hmm. He must
have died later on from...
from a blood clot or something,
that's the only
thing I can figure.
Well... best thing for you to
do is go down and tell the police
what you just told me.
I had a feeling that was what
you were gonna say.
It won't be pleasant,
and your career
probably won't be
on an upswing, but...
they have to know
that if you killed
him on purpose,
you'd be halfway
around the world by now.
You don't think they're
gonna charge me
with murder? No.
Involuntary manslaughter,
maybe, but not-not murder.
D.A.'d never get
a conviction... they'd be
crazy to charge you with that.
First-degree murder?
You're out of your mind!
We have a very strong case.
You're gonna have
to convince a jury
that Ronald Winfield's
death was premeditated.
I know.
But it was an accident.
We can prove otherwise.
But, Julie... We have a witness
who heard Senator Dolan
threaten Winfield over
the phone that day.
We have, uh, Senator
Dolan's statement,
in which he admits getting
into a violent argument
with Winfield that night,
and we have the comic strip,
the one Senator Dolan stole
in hopes of keeping his affair
with Sandra Hopkins a secret.
Yeah, because he gave it to you.
He just wanted to make
himself look innocent.
You mad?
You ruined my hot dog.
Things started getting physical
over here around the desk.
One of us knocked
that bottle of ink down.
Mm.
He hit his head here?
Oh, no, actually, over here
on this side of the fireplace.
And he fell right
around in here.
Yeah? Well, the forensics people
found traces of blood
and hair in two places...
Here and over there.
How many times did you hit him?
Once.
And in the autopsy report,
it said he was hit
in the head twice.
Ben, I only hit
him one time. Huh.
Oh, oh, oh!
What a good dog! Otis,
get off him. Lie down.
You want to get down? You want...
you want to just get down now?
Yeah, yeah.
Oh, I'm...
I'm Ben Matlock,
Senator Dolan's lawyer.
Mickey Alder, Ron
Winfield's assistant. Hello.
Would you mind returning
those strips you stole last night?
Uh, I only took one strip.
You mean more
than one is missing?
You bet. Three weeks' worth.
How do you know? I saw them
sitting on his desk yesterday morning.
When I came by last night
at 9:00, they were gone.
And Ron was dead.
Oh. Uh... Thanks.
Senator, you want to just
run on back to the office,
and I'll meet you
in a little bit. Fine.
So, uh...
you were
Mr. Winfield's assistant?
That's what I said.
You live here?
Your employees live
with you, Mr. Matlock?
No.
I just wondered what you
were doing here at 9:00 at night.
I told you, I was
taking care of the dog.
Ron flew to Miami
yesterday for business,
so I called the house around
8:00, the service picked up,
and I came over
to feed Otis. Oh.
Well, do you know if, uh,
Mr. Winfield called
anybody else yesterday?
Or did anybody call him?
Well, yeah, I know
Senator Dolan called.
He was really mad.
Mm. Anybody else?
Yeah, Senator Hopkins.
What did he want?
Your guess is as good as mine.
Hey, could you do me a favor?
I really need to get
those strips back.
Could you just talk
to Senator Dolan?
He doesn't have them.
Right.
Uh...
What do you want with them?
Well, the people who
syndicate the strip
are interested in taking some
of the already
established characters
and starting a new strip.
You know, since Ron is...
is dead. Mm-hmm.
Who'd draw it?
Well, probably me.
You?
Well, I am a cartoonist.
I mean, I was just working
for Ron for the experience.
You'll have to excuse me.
I've got a lot of things to do.
Got to find Otis a new home.
Do you like dogs?
Not... not that one.
What's her name?
Mickey Alder.
She's going to inherit
Ron Winfield's comic strip?
More or less.
Isn't that a sweet deal?
You think she could
have killed him?
Well, if he was
as woozy as you say
he was when you left,
anybody could have come
in there and shoved his head
in that fireplace one more
time... man or woman.
Maybe I better have a
talk with Sandra Hopkins.
Let's leave her
out of this, please.
Her husband called Ron Winfield
that morning just
after you did. Hmm.
That must mean he knew about Sandra and me.
- Well...
No.
Uh, Mrs. Hopkins?
I'm Michelle Thomas.
I'm one of the attorneys
representing Senator Dolan.
Do you have a minute?
Uh, yes, uh...
I'll meet you outside.
I know about you and
the senator, Mrs. Hopkins.
I guess it's just
a matter of time
before the whole
world knows, isn't it?
Is he all right?
He misses you.
He told me to tell you that.
I've been afraid to call him.
Does your husband know you
and Peter were having an affair?
I don't think so.
He's never said anything to me.
How do you suppose
Ron Winfield found out?
I have no idea.
His cartoon would have hurt
you more than anyone else.
Ms. Thomas, the
night of the murder,
my husband and I
were at a fundraiser.
You can verify this?
Yes.
We were there along
with several thousand
of the governor's
closest friends.
Then, I guess you
didn't kill Mr. Winfield.
No... much as I'd have liked to.
Thanks.
I-I won't keep you any longer.
Uh, tell Peter to...
try not to worry.
Oh, Sandra.
I had to see you.
Have I missed you.
Peter...
Wait, um...
There's something I have to say.
It's over.
We're over.
We should have known better.
We did.
Then we should have done better.
I should have done better.
This is my fault.
I see.
You forced me to
fall in love with you.
Hmm?
Oh, Peter, I'm a coward.
I didn't have the courage
to end a loveless marriage,
or to refuse the
love you offered me.
I thought only of
myself, my career,
how lonely I was
before I met you.
I wanted to hang
on to everything.
Now I've lost everything.
You've still got me.
I never meant...
I know...
To hurt me.
Oh, what is going
to happen to us?
Did you call Ron Winfield
the day he was murdered?
Yes, I called Ron
Winfield that morning.
About what?
About his next strip, of course.
The one where he
was going to reveal
who Senator Dolan
was having an affair with?
We both know it was
my wife, Mr. Matlock.
How long had you known?
About a month.
I suspected she
was seeing someone,
so I hired a
detective to follow her.
Why didn't you confront her?
Mr. Matlock, I've been in
the state senate ten years.
I'm chairman of the
Public Works Committee
and thinking of
running for congress.
I don't need a divorce.
Well, why did you
call Ron Winfield?
I called him because if he
revealed Sandra's indiscretions
the only thing I could
run for is dog catcher.
Oh, you were going to try
to get him to kill the strip.
Damn right.
Only he never returned my call.
Somebody took
care of it for you.
All his murder did for me
was postpone the inevitable.
Or are you going
to try to tell me
my wife's affair won't be
made public during the trial?
Oh, no, no, the cat'll
come out of the bag.
Oh, played golf with
the vice president.
Who won?
I don't remember.
Remember where you were
when Ron Winfield was killed?
My wife and I were at a
very well-attended fundraiser.
From 6:30 to almost midnight.
You know, it's real easy to
slip out of those big parties
unnoticed for a while.
I do it all the time
when I'm bored.
Well, I'll let you
get back to work.
Thanks, Senator.
Come on, boy.
Hello, Otis.
Hello. Otis, get down off him!
Get over here.
I haven't been able to find
anyone to take him yet. Oh.
Well... What can I do for you?
How about letting me in? Okay.
Uh, those strips
that were stolen,
did you ever get a look at 'em?
I got a glance at 'em once.
Well, do you have any
idea who or what your boss
meant to expose next?
No.
Did he keep a diary
or a journal of any kind?
Not that I know of.
We can take a look.
Hey, fella!
Otis, get him. Get him.
Get him, Otis. Get him.
Otis, get him.
Damn.
Well, whatever
he was looking for,
I guess he found it.
What was special
about the word "sunset"?
Sunset?
Yeah, he used it in
almost every strip.
Here, look here,
on the bus bench.
See there?
Oh, yeah.
And here on... I
believe it's the book.
Yeah, see?
Sunset. He never said.
He sure used it a lot.
Ron did stuff like
that all the time.
Here.
Oh, yeah.
Sunset Cleaners, Sunset Camera,
Sunset Flowers, Sunset Mortuary.
There are more than 60
businesses in Atlanta alone
with the word
"sunset" in the name.
And there's a Sunset
Road, a Sunset Place
and a Sunset Avenue.
The man used the word "sunset"
in his strip ten times
in the last six weeks.
That's got to mean something.
It might.
As Dick Tracy used
to say, "I'll check it out."
I want to testify
on my own behalf.
No, you don't.
Yes, I do.
Ben, I'm innocent.
I want to get up
there and tell the truth.
No, you don't.
You'd be opening yourself
up for cross-examination.
The prosecutor would bury you.
I'd have no control
over her questions
or your answers.
I know this lady.
She didn't vote for you.
She believes you're guilty.
I'm an elected official.
Now, I get calls from
angry constituents
and hostile reporters
every single day.
I know how to field questions.
No, you don't.
This is different.
Ben, I have to
get up on the stand
and out loud, under oath,
for the benefit of
everybody who voted for me
and elected me, tell
them that I'm innocent.
I'm against it.
But okay.
Senator Dolan,
did you go to see Ron Winfield
the night he was murdered?
Yes, I did. Uh-huh.
And, uh, when did
you go see him?
I arrived at his house
at approximately 7:30.
Mm-hmm.
Why did you go see him?
To see if he intended
to reveal the identity
of the woman that I'd been
having a relationship with
in the next installment
of his comic strip.
And did he? Yes.
Who was this woman?
Sandra Hopkins.
State Superintendent of Schools.
Yes.
We met last year.
Saw each other on
business several times,
and we fell in love.
Well, what happened when, uh,
Ronald Winfield told you
he was gonna expose
your relationship with her?
I got angry.
He got angry.
Push came to shove, literally.
He hit me, I hit him.
He fell backwards
against the fireplace.
Mm-hmm. Did you hit him
again after that?
No, sir, I did not.
And in what condition was he
when you left?
He was alive...
Conscious and alive.
In fact, he talked to me.
When I took the next
installment of the comic strip
he said go ahead,
because he'd just
draw another one.
What time was that?
It was...
7:40 when I left.
No later. 7:40.
Now...
these photographs are
people's exhibit 23 through 25.
And, uh, they were taken
at approximately
9:40 p.m. at the scene.
Uh, is this
the way you remember
things when you left?
No. In the first place,
Winfield was lying on
the floor on the other side
of the fireplace. Uh-huh.
Anything else?
Yes.
The comic strip I took was
sitting on a stack of others
right here on his desk.
In both of these photos that...
Uh, those strips are gone.
And you didn't take 'em?
No, sir. I just took the one.
Mm-hmm.
Is there anything else,
uh, in these pictures
that's, uh, different from
what you remember?
Yes.
Ron Winfield was alive
when I left the house.
He was conscious.
He was talking.
He was alive.
I did not kill Ron Winfield.
Intentionally or otherwise.
Thank you, Senator.
Your witness.
Senator Dolan, why did you go
to Mr. Winfield's house that night?
As I already said,
to see if he intended
to reveal the identity
of the woman I'd been seeing.
Why didn't you just
call him on the phone?
I did.
His assistant said he
would return my phone call.
He never did.
Did, uh, you use profanity
when you spoke to his assistant?
Yes, I did.
Because you were angry?
Yes.
Why?
Because he was going to
expose my
relationship with Sandra.
That would destroy our careers.
Oh, so what you're saying is,
you didn't go to
Winfield's house
to see if he intended
to expose you,
because you already knew
what he was going to do.
You went there to
stop him, didn't you?
Well, in-in a way, yes.
You argued with him, didn't you?
Yes.
You hit him, didn't you? Yes...
You hit him so hard his head
hit the fireplace, didn't you?
Yes, but that was... You hit him
and you killed him, didn't you?
No!
His hitting his head
like that was an accident.
Then why didn't you
call the paramedics?
Because he was
alive when I left.
You didn't call them
because he was dead.
Just as you intended,
isn't that right,
Senator? Object!
This isn't a question, it's
an argument. Withdrawn.
Nothing further.
Otis!
Get lucky?
Uh, not yet.
You know, those cans
haven't been brought down
to the street since Ron died.
Some of that stuff's
been in there for weeks.
I know.
That's one of the rough drafts
of one of the missing strips.
Did he ever mention anything
about Sunset Condominiums?
Huh-uh.
These trees are, uh...
Birch?
Uh, no, aspen.
Aspen.
Well...
the Sunset Condominiums
are in Aspen.
Senator Hopkins has been
paying taxes and utilities
on a unit owned by
his six-year-old nephew.
Six years old, huh?
Yeah.
What's the good
senator been up to?
He had a two-hour
lunch at his club,
and then he rushed over here.
Didn't Jefferies
Construction just land
some big highway jobs?
A lot. All state-funded.
Think there's a connection?
Oh, yeah, there's a connection.
And it's right there on the
seat of that boy's pants.
Mr. Matlock, is that you?
Yeah.
Otis, get off him! Lie down!
Look at your suit.
It was my favorite.
I'm sorry.
I took him out to the park.
The ground must have been wet.
So, you getting anywhere?
Yeah. I got a pretty
good idea of who did it.
Still I got to prove it.
That's a shame.
It was my favorite and new...
Well, good dog.
Good dog!
Senator Hopkins,
you're chairman
of the Georgia State Senate
Public Works Commitee,
is that right?
That's correct.
Now what does your committee do?
We see to it that the
great state of Georgia gets
the highest-quality roads,
schools and office builidings
at the lowest-possible
cost to the taxpayer.
So you decide what
needs to be built,
and then you solicit bids
from private contractors?
That's correct.
And the lowest bid gets the job?
Not necessarily.
But that usually is the
way it works, isn't it?
Usually, I suppose, yes.
Do you know
about these bids
on ongoing projects?
I have nothing to do
with the selection process.
You could find out if you
wanted to, couldn't you?
If I wanted to, yes, but, uh...
Are you familiar
with Jefferies
Construction Company?
Yes, they've done
work for the state.
Ten public-funded jobs
in the last two years.
Bid on 12, got ten.
I'd say that's
something of a record.
Not only was their bid
the lowest, it was the last.
Almost as if someone were
keeping them informed on the bid
so that they could be sure
and ease theirs in just under.
That's impossible.
Why?
Because that's illegal.
Yeah, but, but, someone could
keep the president of
Jefferies Construction informed
on the bid, so that
he could be certain
that his company's was
the lowest, couldn't he?
How about you, Senator?
Absolutely not. Objection!
This is completely
irresponsible.
Nothing in Mr. Matlock's
question has anything
to do with the evidence!
I tell you what, Your Honor,
if you'll allow me to
continue, I'll prove it.
Overruled for now.
In the last six
weeks of his life,
Ron Winfield planted
the word "sunset"
ten times in his comic strip.
See on the billboard there
and on the bus stop bench
and on the book? Why
would he do that, huh?
How about this?
He wanted to remind
one of his readers
that he knew something
about that reader
that he could make
public at any time.
It was kind of a code.
A secret message,
wasn't it, Senator?
I don't know what on
Earth you're talking about.
Last year, the president
of Jefferies Construction
bought a condominium
at Aspen, Colorado,
for a half-million dollars.
But he didn't
buy it for himself.
He signed it over
to someone else.
to a person named
Joel Martin, your
six-year-old nephew.
I don't know
anything about this.
Are you saying that
wasn't a kickback?
Of course it wasn't.
That it was just a coincidence?
It must be.
That the president of
Jefferies Construction wasn't
paying you back for all
those big fat jobs you got them
with a big fat
chunk of real estate?
Absolutely not.
You're saying that it's a
coincidence that the name
of the condominium
project at Aspen is Sunset?
All I know is I've
done nothing wrong,
and I bitterly resent
these allegations.
Ron Winfield found out
about your arrangement
with Jefferies Construction.
There is no arrangment.
He was blackmailing
you, wasn't he?
No.
Only he didn't want cash,
he wanted dirt...
Inside information on political
shenanigans he could use
in his comic strip.
And you knew if you didn't
come through, he'd expose you.
And that would not only
mean the end of your job,
you'd go to jail.
So you gave him what he wanted.
Is that how he found
out about your wife's affair
with Senator Dolan?
Are you out of your mind?
Over and over again,
he used the word
"sunset" in his comic strip.
It must have driven you
crazy trying to figure out
what he'd do next.
And so finally, that night
you went over to
his house, didn't you?
I did no such thing.
I don't know what
you had in mind
when you went into that room,
but I'm pretty sure that when
you saw that he was hurt,
and he told you that
Senator Dolan had done it,
you hit his head in that
fireplace a second time
and killed him.
And then you took
the comic strips
so that no one would
be able to connect you
with the condominium at Aspen.
That's a lie!
And knowing that Ron
Winfield kept solid evidence
to back the allegations
in his comic strip,
you sent someone from
Jefferies Construction
to ransack his house,
steal the evidence,
and destroy it, didn't you?
Everything you just
said is an out-and-out lie!
You didn't go to
his house that night?
I've never been to Ron
Winfield's house in my life.
Never? Never.
Would you tell the court
whose suit jacket this is?
It looks like mine.
It is mine.
Where did you get it?
The police with a warrant
took it from your closet
this morning after you left.
Is this the suit you wore
to his house that night?
I just told you I have never
been to Ron Winfield's house.
Why'd you take it to the
cleaners the next morning?
I don't remember.
Well, right here's the receipt.
See? "8:45 A.M., April seventh."
That's the day after the murder.
It says, "Remove
stain on jacket front."
Ron Winfield had a dog,
big friendly dog named "Otis."
Liked to jump up on everybody
who came into the room
and get dirt on your jacket.
Have to take it to the cleaners.
During the fight with
Mr. Winfield and Senator Dolan,
a bottle of ink got
knocked off on the floor.
See the ink there?
The dog must have
walked through it.
See his pawprints?
What if that dog
walked through that ink
after Senator Dolan
left and jumped up on
the next person to
come into the room...
The real killer?
Why, he'd get, he'd
get ink on his suit front.
Have to go to the cleaners.
I spilled coffee on my suit.
Maybe so.
The cleaner was unable to say.
It wasn't ink, Mr. Matlock.
Now for the last time, I
was not at that house.
That night or any other night.
How about this?
This is a piece of Ron
Winfield's stationery.
Officer Danny Levine's
prepared to testify that he found it
in the pocket of this suit
this morning when he
took it from your home.
And a handwriting
expert is prepared to testify
that this is Ron
Winfield's handwriting.
This is a list of calls
he received the day
he was murdered.
You took this
because you didn't
want anyone to know
that you were so
anxious to talk to him
that you called him
five times that day.
You took this and
the comic strips
after you killed
him, didn't you?
We find the
defendant not guilty.
Having found the
defendant not guilty,
this court is adjourned.
Thank you, both
of you, very much.
Now you can get
on with your life.
What's left of it.
I still have a feeling
I'm gonna have
to step down even with
the not-guilty verdict.
There are a lot of
reporters out here.
Want me to run
interference for you?
No, that's all right.
I got to face the
music sometime.
It might as well be now.
Thank you again. Bye.
I'll go with you.
www.tvsubtitles.net